WEB DEVELOPER

About —

I am an experienced PHP developer with 5 years of in depth experience on both front end and back end work

I have advanced skills in PHP, MvSQL. Javascript, HTML, JQuery, and CSS to name a few. I have completed a Bachelor of Science in Information Technology and completed numerous projects for different companies since college.

Contact -

- +639159594496
- neilpatrickendonilacruz@gmail.com
- /neil-patrick-cruz-412471a8

Education —

Jose Rizal University

BS in Information Technology

2008 - 2014

80 Shaw Blvd, Mandaluyong, 1552 Metro Manila

Pateros National High School

2004 - 2008

320 P. Herrera, Pateros, 1620 Metro Manila

Pateros Elementary School

1998 - 2004

P. Herrera, San Pendro, Pateros, 1620 Metro Manila

Work Experience -

Aug 2015 - Present

Esprow

Front-end Developer

Esprow is a leading global provider of testing and compliance automation solutions for the financial industry. The Esprow Enterprise Testing Platform (Esprow ETP) provides an integrated suite of applications to automate testing of multi-protocol financial systems, on-boarding and certification of counterparties and native exchange and broker simulation.

May 2014 - Aug 2015

August99, Inc.

Wordpress/PHP Developer

August 99 is a tight-knit team of web experts from Manila. Philippines. It is a boutique of Internet marketing and web design outsourcing company.

June 2013 - May 2014

Ivant Technologies

Front-end Developer

Ivant Technologies is a Philippine-based provider of complete internet consulting and software services. The clients that the company cater to are from both the local and the international market.

Oct 2011 - June 2013

Topgrafikas

Wordpress/PHP Developer

It's a team of freelancer in Jose Rizal University that cater web development. Even while we are still studying we opt to explore the business at a young age.

HTML / CSS:



Bootstrap



Semantic-UI



Foundation



Materialize



Skeleton

Javascript:



Query



Node.js



Angular JS



Express



Meteor JS





mongoDB

PHP:



Wordpress



Codeigniter





MySQL





Sublime Text



Chrome Dev Tools



MAMP



GitHub



Photoshop